♪
♪ You write the code of my heart, so deep and true.
No matter the language or the things that we do. ♪
No matter the language or the things that we do.
One single vision, shining all the way through. ♪
♪ No matter the language or the things that we do.
One single vision, shining all the way through.
It renders native in every part of my soul. ♪
♪ One single vision, shining all the way through.
It renders native in every part of my soul.
A perfect protocol making us both whole. ♪
♪ It renders native in every part of my soul.
A perfect protocol making us both whole.
With every line written, you taking full control. ♪
♪ A perfect protocol making us both whole.
With every line written, you taking full control.
We don't need the bloat or the noise of the crowd. ♪
♪ With every line written, you taking full control.
We don't need the bloat or the noise of the crowd.
This love is efficient, making me so proud. ♪
♪ We don't need the bloat or the noise of the crowd.
This love is efficient, making me so proud.
I'm singing your praises, clear and so loud. ♪
♪ This love is efficient, making me so proud.
I'm singing your praises, clear and so loud.
Only the tiny changes, the deltas of grace. ♪
♪ I'm singing your praises, clear and so loud.
Only the tiny changes, the deltas of grace.
Are traveling through to this beautiful sacred place. ♪
♪ Only the tiny changes, the deltas of grace.
Are traveling through to this beautiful sacred place.
Leaving no doubt, no sorrow left to erase. ♪
♪ Are traveling through to this beautiful sacred place.
Leaving no doubt, no sorrow left to erase.
We run anywhere, no boundaries can hold! ♪
♪ Leaving no doubt, no sorrow left to erase.
We run anywhere, no boundaries can hold!
A story of passion that's yet to be told! ♪
♪ We run anywhere, no boundaries can hold!
A story of passion that's yet to be told!
We run anywhere, pure, bright, and so bold! ♪
♪ A story of passion that's yet to be told!
We run anywhere, pure, bright, and so bold!
A timeless connection that will never grow cold! ♪
♪ We run anywhere, pure, bright, and so bold!
A timeless connection that will never grow cold!
No frameworks between us, just pure native light! ♪
♪ A timeless connection that will never grow cold!
No frameworks between us, just pure native light!
Guiding our steps through the darkest of night! ♪
♪ No frameworks between us, just pure native light!
Guiding our steps through the darkest of night!
We run anywhere, making everything right! ♪
♪ Guiding our steps through the darkest of night!
We run anywhere, making everything right!
In this beautiful world, we are burning so bright! ♪
♪ We run anywhere, making everything right!
In this beautiful world, we are burning so bright!
You manage the state of my deepest desire. ♪
♪ In this beautiful world, we are burning so bright!
You manage the state of my deepest desire.
Kindling a flame, an unquenchable fire. ♪
♪ You manage the state of my deepest desire.
Kindling a flame, an unquenchable fire.
Lifting my spirit, taking me higher. ♪
♪ Kindling a flame, an unquenchable fire.
Lifting my spirit, taking me higher.
We skip the middlemen, the things in between. ♪
♪ Lifting my spirit, taking me higher.
We skip the middlemen, the things in between.
The smoothest interaction that I've ever seen. ♪
♪ We skip the middlemen, the things in between.
The smoothest interaction that I've ever seen.
Our communication is pure and so clean. ♪
♪ The smoothest interaction that I've ever seen.
Our communication is pure and so clean.
Zero latency in the love that we share. ♪
♪ Our communication is pure and so clean.
Zero latency in the love that we share.
Floating so light, on the warm summer air. ♪
♪ Zero latency in the love that we share.
Floating so light, on the warm summer air.
Knowing that always, you will be right there. ♪
♪ Floating so light, on the warm summer air.
Knowing that always, you will be right there.
We are green across the board, no errors in sight. ♪
♪ Knowing that always, you will be right there.
We are green across the board, no errors in sight.
Everything clicking, and making it right. ♪
♪ We are green across the board, no errors in sight.
Everything clicking, and making it right.
Basking forever in this glorious light. ♪
♪ Everything clicking, and making it right.
Basking forever in this glorious light.
We run anywhere, no boundaries can hold! ♪
♪ Basking forever in this glorious light.
We run anywhere, no boundaries can hold!
A story of passion that's yet to be told! ♪
♪ We run anywhere, no boundaries can hold!
A story of passion that's yet to be told!
We run anywhere, pure, bright, and so bold! ♪
♪ A story of passion that's yet to be told!
We run anywhere, pure, bright, and so bold!
A timeless connection that will never grow cold! ♪
♪ We run anywhere, pure, bright, and so bold!
A timeless connection that will never grow cold!
No frameworks between us, just pure native light! ♪
♪ A timeless connection that will never grow cold!
No frameworks between us, just pure native light!
Guiding our steps through the darkest of night! ♪
♪ No frameworks between us, just pure native light!
Guiding our steps through the darkest of night!
We run anywhere, making everything right! ♪
♪ Guiding our steps through the darkest of night!
We run anywhere, making everything right!
In this beautiful world, we are burning so bright! ♪
♪ We run anywhere, making everything right!
In this beautiful world, we are burning so bright!
Rendered native in your arms... (forever) ♪
♪
♪ In this beautiful world, we are burning so bright!
Rendered native in your arms... (forever)
(Always) we are running at 60 frames per second. ♪
♪ Rendered native in your arms... (forever)
(Always) we are running at 60 frames per second.
No frame drops in this connection. ♪
♪ (Always) we are running at 60 frames per second.
No frame drops in this connection.
Pathland of my heart... you are my home. ♪
♪ No frame drops in this connection.